http://www.fathersloveletter.com/privacy-policy.html

Devotionals
FathersLoveLetter.com Privacy PolicyFather Heart Communications operates http://www.FathersLoveLetter.comThis page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of our website. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using FathersLoveLetter.com you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.Log DataWhen accessing web pages on our website, our website host, Weebly may log your IP address, access URL, time of access, geographic location, browser type, and referral URL in order to provide us with internal information regarding site traffic statistics. This information may also be used to identify users who are using the service for spam or other activity that is deemed in conflict with our Terms of Service. Otherwise, this information is used in the aggregate, and is never linked back to any personally identifiable information. To ready the Weebly.com privacy policy, click here.CookiesCookies are text files stored on your computer, and accessible only to the websites which create them. Our website may from time to time use cookies and log files for statistical analysis, to understand user behaviour, to administer the site, to tailor the information presented to a user based on their preferences, and to improve user experience.  Any information gathered by our use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, however you may delete, or disable cookies by following the instructions at http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/.  Google AnalyticsOur website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). The information generated by the cookie about your use of our website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  Further information about Google’s privacy policy may be obtained from http://www.google.com/privacy.html. To opt-out of Google Analytics, you can do so here.Social MediaThis Website provides users the opportunity to interact and post content through various social media sites including, but not limited to, Twitter, Facebook, Google+, Instagram, Dropbox, Tumblr, foursquare, Flickr, MediaFire, YouTube and Vimeo. Your interactions with such tools, and any information you provide in connection with these interactions are publicly viewable outside of the Website domain. Each social media site has its own privacy policies which may be more or less protective than this Policy. If you do not wish for this information to be disclosed, then you should not use these tools. We are not responsible for information you choose to post in these forums.Paypal DonationsIf you decide to make a donation to Father Heart Communications through our secure Paypal link, your data is encrypted and secure and is subject to the Paypal.com privacy policy.Third Party Online StoresThis website provides external links to the following 3rd party online stores... Amazon.com / CrownEntertainment.us / MoodyPublishers.com / Crossway.org. Please refer to each online store's own privacy policy to find out more information about the data they collect.Changes To This Privacy PolicyFather Heart Communications may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.Acceptance Of This Privacy PolicyIf you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use our site. By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like more information about how your data is tracked, please send us a message through our contact page. This Privacy Policy was last modified on May 21, 2018
About Us
AboutThe StoryCopyright
Get Involved
FAQTerms of UseOur Websites
Connect
ContactPrivacy PolicyDonate
© COPYRIGHT 2020. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
